Introduction
Chapter 1 Understanding God’s Desire to Communicate Personally
Chapter 2 The Many Forms of Revelation and How They Are Recognized
Chapter 3 Principles and Patterns of Divine Communication
Chapter 4 Distinguishing God’s Voice from Other Influences
Chapter 5 Building Faith Through Spiritual Experience and Obedience
Chapter 6 Creating an Environment for Revelation
Chapter 7 Overcoming Barriers to Receiving Revelation
Chapter 8 Deepening the Conversation—Asking Better Questions
Chapter 9 Sustaining Revelation in Daily Living
Chapter 10 Sharing and Supporting Others in Their Spiritual Journey
Conclusion